TONNY ANDRIAMBOLOLONA

WEB DEVELOPER / DESIGNER

+1 438 722 6839

tonny.mtrl@gmail.com

444tonny.github.io/Portfolio

ABOUT ME

With over 2 years of experience in web development, both in corporate environments and as a freelancer, I am actively seeking new professional challenges. I am eager to apply my skills and satisfy my continuous desire for learning.

SKILLS

- UI/UX & Web Design
 - o HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Responsive design
 - o Figma, Adobe Photoshop & XD
- Full Stack Development
 - JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, C#
 - o Framework: Laravel, VueJS, AngularJS
 - o CMS: WordPress
 - Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Deployment, Administration & Migration of websites
 - o Github, GitLab, Linux CLI

EDUCATION

• 2018 - 2021: Bachelor's Degree in Web Development & Design

IT University (Madagascar)

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Lifetime Travel

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022

Designer & Developer

- Designed Logo + UI/UX + Database structure
- Development of Client and Admin Websites

Technical support for employees

Kaki Agency

Mar 2022 - May 2022

Web Integrator

- Integration of WordPress Websites

Upwork (Freelance)

Since June 2022

Full Stack Developer

- Designing and Coding multiple websites for clients worldwide
- Deployment, optimization & maintenance of websites

SOFT SKILLS

Detail-oriented, collaborative, autonomous, creative, & well-organized

LANGUAGES

• French: Native

• English: Advanced